

# **CONTACTS**

**\( +38 098 461 7282** 

<u>chornyalexander@gmail.com</u>

www.chorny-alexander/

in Alexander Chorny

Vinnitsa, Ukraine

## **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS
  - responsive
  - valid
  - cross-browser
- JavaScript
  - React
- Figma, Photoshop
- Git

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English Intermediate
- German Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native

# **ALEXANDER CHORNY**

# **WEB DEVELOPER**

#### **PROFILE**

I am a developer with good experience with HTML, CSS and JS. I strive to create reliable, adaptive, cross-browser web products based on best practices and accessibility.

In life, I enjoy self-learning and therefore I try to develop, both in terms of technical skills and communication skills. So I plan my days to improve my frontend development skills, learn and use tools to speed up web development and improve my language skills (English and German).

I feel the need to learn anything new or do something useful in a day. Moreover I like doing sports and developing in various directions: swimming, running, strength training.

## **EXPERIENCE**

jan 2023 - up to now

#### FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

HTML · CSS · JavaScript · React · Figma, Photoshop · Git

jul 2015 - feb 2022

**MYHOBBY** 

#### **CONSULTANT MANAGER**

Website maintenance, consultations, sales, purchase of goods.

apr 2015 - jun 2015

APPAREL EXPRESS

# **IMPROVEMENT OF A WEBSITE**

Improvement of website design and functionality. Refinement of the order sorting module.

dec 2014 - feb 2015

KRAINEVA ANASTASIA

#### **WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT**

Website development for an artist.

## **EDUCATION**

November 2022 - up to now | USA **JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures** FreeCodeCamp

September 2022 - November 2022 | USA

**Responsive Web Design** 

FreeCodeCamp